

DENIS HANIF PRASETYA

I've an experience as Photocopier Engineering for 6 years, and have experience as IT Support less than 1 year. Skilled in network and PC maintenance, writing, teamwork & communication. I also willing to be open minded, happy to discuss and able to work individually as well as in team.

Place, Date of Birth: Tegal, 04-10-1996

Religion : Moslem Marital Status: Single

REACH ME AT

Kec. Tambun Utara, Kab. Bekasi, 17511
(+62) 813 1922 9466

dnshaniff@gmail.com (Email)

linkedin.com/in/denis-hanif-prasetya7a815516b (LinkedIn)

WORK EXPERIENCE

dnshaniff.github.io (Portfolio)

PT. Garuda Mas Rentalindo

Photocopier Engineering 30 June 2014 - 25 February 2021

- Do installation of Konica Minolta Multifunction Printers
- Maintenance and service Photocopier
- Network installation (Connection Printer/Scanner to Computer)

PT. Marsit Bangun Sejahtera

IT Support

22 September 2021 - 31 December 2021

- Assist the marketing team regrading application usage and it's problems
- Write test case for application
- Network installation (Connection Printer/Scanner to Computer)
- Ensure the internet networks and IPBX telephone are running well
- Manage Database (phpMyAdmin)
- Responsible for printers and projectors
- Managing IT digital assets (SMS Gateway, Google Cloud Platform, and Niaga Hoster)

EDUCATION

Mercu Buana University

2017 - 2021

Faculty of Computer Science Informatics Engineering

SMK Malaka

2011 - 2014

Computer Network Engineering

SKILLS

- Computer and peripheral (disassembly and assembly)
- Windows Installation
- Troubleshooting PC & networking
- HTML and CSS
- Java Script
- PHP (Codeigniter)
- DBMS (MySQL)
- Vector design (Adobe Illustrator)

CERTIFICATION

Udemy

August, 2021

PHP & MySQL - Certification Course for Beginners

Cisco Networking Academy

March, 2020

CCNA Routing and Switching: Introduction to Network

EC - Council

August, 2017

Certificate Secure Computer User v2